A Guide to the Bondurant-Morrison Family Papers
University of Virginia Library
- Bound Volumes
  - B.V.'s: School Notebooks
    - Greek and Mathematics Notes of Henry Rutherford Morrison and Accounts, 1861, 1876-1879 (Box Box 48)
    - Hebrew Exercises of Alexander Lee Bondurant (Box Box 48)
    - Latin Final Exercises of Alexander Lee Bondurant, 1885 (Box Box 48)
    - Latin Notes of Alexander Lee Bondurant (Box Box 48)
    - Latin Exercises of Alexander Lee Bondurant, 1887-1888 (Box Box 48)
    - Latin Exercises of Alexander Lee Bondurant (Box Box 48)
    - Latin Exercises of Alexander Lee Bondurant (Box Box 48)
    - Lectures on Metres of Lewis M. Dabney, n.d. (Box Box 48)
    - Lecture Notes and Accounts of George P. Bondurant, 1859-1872 (Box Box 48)
    - Biblical Literature Notes of Alexander Lee Bondurant at the University of Texas, 1885-1886 (Box Box 49)
    - Lectures on Literature to the Senior Class by Alexander Lee Bondurant, 1887-1888 (Box Box 49)
    - Logic Notes of Alexander Lee Bondurant (Box Box 49)
    - Logic Notes of Alexander Lee Bondurant (Box Box 49)
    - Medical School Notes of Thomas L. Bondurant, 1856 (Box Box 49)
    - "Materia Medica" Notes of Thomas L. Bondurant, 1856-1857 (Box Box 49)
    - Physics Notes of [Dabney (Bondurant) Hare] (Box Box 49)
    - Psychology Notes of Alexander Lee Bondurant at the University of Virginia, 1887-1888 (Box Box 49)
    - Psychology Notes of Alexander Lee Bondurant (Box Box 49)
- Oversize Bound Volumes
  - Buckingham County Court Cases and Decisions, 1824-1827 (Box Box 49)
  - Ledger of [Thomas M. Bondurant], 1830-1831 (Box Box 49)
  - Ledger of [Thomas M. Bondurant] and Farm Book, 1835, 1841-1847 (Box Box 49)
  - Ledger of B.M.P. & Co., 1850 (Box Box 49)
  - Farm Book for Variety Shade and Black-Rock, kept by George P. Bondurant, including blacksmith accounts, 1867, 1851-1873 (Box Box 49)
  - Journal of goods sold of Alexander J. Bondurant, Mt. Vinco, 1865-1867 (Box Box 49)
  - Journal of the Richmond Whig, 1865-1873 (Box Box 49)
  - Letterbook of Alexander J. Bondurant, Re: Agriculture, 1895-1901 (Box Box 49)
- Oversize Folder
  - Buckingham County Land Grant to Joseph Cabell, signed by Gov. Beverly Randolph, 1787 Aug 24
  - Buckingham County Land Grant to John Gary, signed by Gov. Thomas Mann Randolph, 1822 Dec 2
  - Census of Colored Children up to the age of twenty-one, [Buckingham County], 1885
  - Document for appointment of Fanny B. Bondurant as postmaster at Variety Shade in Buckingham County, 1889 Dec 12
  - Broadside for "King Lear" a horse to be sold by Chas. D. Diggs, Cumberland County, Va., 1890
  - Diploma of honorable mention from the Columbian Exposition to Alexander J. Bondurant, 1895
  - Invitations from the Government of Victoria for the "Royal Review" and the opening of Parliament in Melbourne, Australia, 1901
  - Plot and survey of Black-Rock for Alexander Lee Bondurant, 1910
  - Map of the Richmond and Danville Railway System